phonespamfilter.co.uk 2014-06-21

# Phone Spam Filter Privacy Policy

## Search Phone Numbers

_Note:_ We have 10,000+ phone numbers, and we want more. Add your own complaints now!

* * *

**★ Spread the word**

Click the button below to add PhoneSpamFilter.co.uk to your shared bookmark service. 

* * *

Terms of Use   
Privacy Policy

PhoneSpamFilter.co.uk has established this privacy policy to explain to you how your information is protected, collected and used, which may be updated by phonespamfilter from time to time. phonespamfilter will provide notice of materially significant changes to this privacy policy by posting notice on the phonespamfilter site. 

#### 1\. Protecting your privacy

  * We don't share your information with third parties for marketing purposes. 
  * We don't send you unsolicited communications for marketing purposes. 
  * phonespamfilter does not knowingly collect any information from persons under the age of 13. If phonespamfilter learns that a posting is by a person under the age of 13, phonespamfilter will remove that post. 
  * phonespamfilter, or people who post on phonespamfilter, may provide links to third party websites, which may have different privacy practices. We are not responsible for, nor have any control over, the privacy policies of those third party websites, and encourage all users to read the privacy policies of each and every website visited. 

#### 2\. Data we collect

  * We sometimes collect your email address, for purposes such as sending self-publishing and confirmation emails, authenticating user accounts, providing subscription email services, registering for forums, etc. 
  * phonespamfilter does not store credit card information. Credit card transactions are transmitted to a financial gateway, and we endeavor to protect the security of your payment information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. 
  * We may collect personal information if you provide it in feedback or comments, post it on our interactive forums, or if you contact us directly. Please do not post any personal information on phonespamfilter's forums or classifieds that you expect to keep private. 
  * Our web logs collect standard web log entries for each page served, including your IP address, page URL, and timestamp. Web logs help us to diagnose problems with our server, to administer the phonespamfilter site, and to otherwise provide our service to you. 

#### 3\. Data we store

  * All postings are stored in our database, even after "deletion," and may be archived elsewhere. 
  * Our web logs and other records are stored indefinitely. 
  * Although we make good faith efforts to store the information in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public, we cannot guarantee complete security. 

#### 4\. Archiving and display of phonespamfilter postings by search engines and other sites

Search engines and other sites not affiliated with phonespamfilter - including archive.org, google.com and yahoo.com - archive or otherwise make available postings. 

#### 5\. Circumstances in which phonespamfilter may release information

  * PhoneSpamFilter.co.uk may disclose information about its users if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. 
  * PhoneSpamFilter.co.uk may also disclose information about its users to law enforcement officers or others, in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms of Use; respond to claims that any posting or other content violates the rights of third-parties; or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of phonespamfilter, its users or the general public. 

#### 6\. International Users

By visiting our web site and providing us with data, you acknowledge and agree that due to the international dimension of phonespamfilter we may use the data collected in the course of our relationship for the purposes identified in this policy or in our other communications with you, including the transmission of information outside your resident jurisdiction. In addition, please understand that such data may be stored on servers located in the United States. By providing us with your data, you consent to the transfer of such data.
